Doble, William J. Papers 5182
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Employee Self-Discipline as a Part of Education and Accident Prevention Program, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Consolidation of Ohio Division and Ohio Central Div. Seniority Roster, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Expense Claims, 1955-1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Elkhard Signal Shop
- Time and Half Pay Claim, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Petty Larceny - Personal File, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Complaint About Denial of Claims Indianapolis Union Railroad, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Automatic Snow Collectors, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Working Conditions, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Discipline Hearing. Employee's Failure to Inspect Relay Circuit Resulting in Accident, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Removal of Positions, Sheldon, 111., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Inspector-Foremen Membership in Craft Locals, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Dues
- Federal Legislation Concerning Railroad Employees, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Rate of Pay for 'Maintainers in Charge', 1943-1951 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- R.L. Nunn - Disciplinary Action, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Splicing Work Done by Leading Signal Mechanic, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Testing Highway Crossing Signals in Canada, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Inspector-Foremen Performing Craft Work, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- I.H.B. - Labor Relations, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Accident Liability Benefit Claims, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Transfer of Signal Sections, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Change in Managerial Jurisdiction (North District), 1958 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Discipline Case, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- NRAB, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Personal Injury Claim, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Work Jurisdiction, 1953-1961 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Lodge 15 - Company Trucks, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Work Jurisdiction Claim, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Seniority Rights, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Differential Pay Rates for Craft Employees, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Transfer of Maintenance Sections from Illinois (P&E) to Indiana Division, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Agreement including Hot Box Defectors, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Position Bid and Expense Claim, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Suspension as Discipline, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- State Legislative Counsels, 1952-1961 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Supplemental 3rd Division, NRAB, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Sanford Mullins vs. NYC Railroad, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- NYC/IHB Agreement, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  claims and correspondence
- Work Holiday at Straight Time, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Clarification of Memorandum of Craft Agreement, Gang Assignments, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  -
- Force Reduction due to Picketing of the NYC by Maritime Unions, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- UROC (United Railroad Operating Crafts), 1958 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Abolishment of Cleveland Signal District and Allocation of Seniority Rights, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Veteran's Re-employment Rights, 1953-1962 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Application of Vacation and Holiday Pay Rules (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Representation Authorization Form (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Consolidation of Locals 30 and 41, Ohio Division, 1954-1960 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Stealing Tools from Trucks, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Duplicate Claims (Box 10, Folder 51)
- LMRDA, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Agreement - Wages and Vacations, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Claim - C.G. Spencer, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Toilet Facilities at Michigan City, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Transfer of Signal Sections to Toledo Signal District, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Forced Promotions of Assistants, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Electronic Technicians, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- P & E, Illinois Division; Transfer of Positions, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- NYC Incorporated in State of Delaware, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Lateness of Paychecks, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Protesting Headquarters, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Transfer of District from Chicago Terminal to Indiana Div., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Levermen's Desire to Join Brhd. of Railroad Signalmen, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Wage Request, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Hydro-Crane - Purchase and Operation of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- NYC; M.C. Big Four Agreement, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- P & LE, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- I.G.R. Railroad, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Case Files on Union Shop Agreement, 1951-1955 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Hiring and Firing, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Letters to Local Financial Secretaries, 1951-1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Termination of Employment, 1952-1959 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Removals from Service - New York Central, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Big 4, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- P & LE, 1952-1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Michigan Central, 1951-1960 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Michigan Central Big 4 Indiana Division, 1951-1962 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions, 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  New York Central
- Big 4, 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- I.H.B., 1951-1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Michigan Central, 1951-1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Local 83, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Local 96, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Local 128, 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Local 210, 1952-1956 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- I.H.B. 1951 Agreement, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Revision to I.H.B. Agreement, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Committee on Resolutions, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- New York Central, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Local Wiring Work
- P & LE Employee Seniority, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- P & LE Miscellenaous Correspondence and Agreements, 1951-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- New York Central - Income Accounts, 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Agreements (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Foreman Agreements, 1931-1933 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- General Electric Company (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Wage and Force Reductions, 1930-1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Railway Labor Executive Association, 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Maintainer Units, 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 35th Regular Convention, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- New York Central, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Big Four, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- NRAB Cases, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Ballots on the Work Week (Box 13, Folder 5)
- I. H. B. Railroad, 1931-1935 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Report of General Chairman, 1933-1938 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New York Central Railroad - Working Time, 1932-1934 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- I.H.B., 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Schedules, 1930-1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Michigan Central, 1931-1934 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Signal Inspection Lav (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Third Division, NRAB Settlement of Work Week (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Wage Controversy, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Wage Increase, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Directory of General Chairman (Box 14, Folder 1)
- PANYC Merger - Text of Agreement (Box 14, Folder 2)
- PANYC Merger - Related Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- PANYC Merger - Related Publications (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Record Books (Box 15)
- Phonodiscs, pamphlets, record book, etc. (Box 16)